your child can get sick when you don't
at night but you don't have money but if
you you are on insurance you just take
that child get full proper
treatment on that insurance in any case
it seems you have you have paid so much
little yet you are getting each
treatment you want you just go to their
service providers and get
treatment everything Physiotherapy x-ray
M on that 1 million which is ridiculous
I feel but that's how it
is my name is Glades
Nanda I
am nearly 60 years 2022 June I joined
the presedential medical insurance I
have a young sister who works in a bank
so the connection was was through and sh
an account in Stan so we joined him
presidential as a family and our mates
and the workers I feel that everybody
should be on medical
insurance and I know that it's it's very
difficult this concept of having maybe 1
million at a go and you pay it
there or 600,000 ATO and you pay it
there because people feel or we feel
that illness is like
rational some say I'm not sick I cannot
I may not get sick the whole year but
you never know I've been on medical
insurance for a long time because it's
cheap the cheapest of all the medical
insurance yet it's giving and it's
giving much more than most of them
that's what that's what I feel and I'm
very happy with with this medical
insurance last year
2024 I got a very serious
disease connected with our
bones and I
feel this this leg in Fe was not walking
were carrying me in
everywhere and I feel that this
insurance because I was on
insurance it helped me a lot because
usually bone diseases are very very
expensive the physiotherapy the
medicine if I was to pay out of the my
pocket it would have cost me like 3
million because the medicine give you
medicine for 200,000 that's for one
month then you go back they give you and
you understand
so I believe that everybody should be on
medical insurance because think about it
if you are paying 1 million for your a
year and maybe you getting treatment
beyond that 1 million it is serving you
really your child can get sick when you
don't at night but you don't have money
but if you you are on insurance you just
take that child get full proper
treatment on that insurance I don't know
if I can say this I feel that if
if I'm not on medical insurance it's
like I'm not having a mobile phone or
I'm walking around naked it has become
part of me and I encourage I encourage
encourage if you are not on any medical
insurance please please think about it
it saves a lot of money thank you
presedential
medical
insurance for all you have done for me
and I'm very very happy with you
[Music]